I know I said nikka Nicholas Amida on
this video we are gonna do a Q&A last
week on our YouTube channel and on our
Instagram and on our slack channel we
announce that we're going to record this
video and we got too many questions so
I'm going to try to answer as many as I
can
let's get started so my daily routine
before corner and after Corona changed
so now that is corona time I just wake
up walk this dog over here and then come
back home and literally work all the way
until the afternoon I eat one time per
day so I use cook dinner at night and
then I walk the dog again at night and
that's it I don't really have a hobby
apart from reading books I really like
reading books nowadays and also I enjoy
watching like really good movies I'm not
so into serious but I'd really like
cinema I have never been good at
mathematics at all I think the most
memorable project is the one I'm
currently working on right now which is
I'm trying to just make the whole
website of the academy of normal colors
again from zero and also I'm gonna make
the new challenges and maybe a mobile
applications and that's a pretty big
massive project that I'm very excited
about Papago because I need to translate
many things when I live when I when I
see Korean text-heavy that'd be okay
people ask me this question a lot like
why do I say Anya has a gyro or why I'd
say kimchi or why am I in Korea well the
answer is that I live in Korea I have a
Korean wife and her family is Korean and
I love that family and I also have
friends in Korea so yes that's why yes
there are many paid courses in my brain
coming soon I want to make a surrealist
course really where are you going there
many coaches I want to make but I just
don't have the time I want to make
serverless course I want to make also
more go long course I was thinking maybe
cloning and like a crypto currency
exchange in Golan that'll be super
exciting but yeah there is no time but
there are all coming slowly slowly
slowly and also have to update many
courses so also that thing as well I
don't know what I do I like learning
languages so maybe I'll be speaking many
languages but nothing else apart from
that I don't think I can do anything
else maybe taking photographs I don't
know okay development wise I really want
to finish the project that I'm currently
working on which is making the whole
nomads coders and lifeWise I really
would like to I don't know become more
Korean I would like to be able to
understand the culture more I want to be
able to speak the language I want to be
able to have more Korean friends and
have like a normal Korean life sometime
that I don't know anything about coffee
whatsoever so I just drink any coffee a
favorite game is go stop but I really
enjoy playing cost of is really it give
me adrenaline rush it's really fun every
day as much as I can
correct I don't think I am going to
clean samgyupsal
I'm good at eating samgyeopsal if you
want to go and have some pizza with me
let's go together
Pizza jumpin i deep black I only have
black panties yes I was born with long
hair you can ask my mom
any scratches fine this big lean of
course
I got a medium I go to Reddit I go to
hacker news especially in reddit because
there are many subreddits so that means
that you can follow JavaScript Python
react whatever that is there is where
everybody goes to like share anything
new in library and you write if you feel
overwhelmed with a new take the best
thing you can do is to stop learning new
tech you don't have to learn new tech
all the time using boring tech most of
the time is the best tool for the job so
you don't have to be learned keep on
learning many many things and updating
and updating you don't have to you just
just look at things for maybe a couple
hours look at what they are about but
you don't have to learn them all right
just focus on your core what is your
core
are you a Python developer are you a
goal developer are you a Java developer
and focus on your core the rest can be
on your radar but you should learn
everything new that's just the recipe
for Berna there are structures and
algorithms are important because be in a
programmer and being able to implement
your own data structures or being able
to be good at logic and algorithms it's
just good gym for your brain so that's
it if you are good at that you are going
to solve problems easier also people are
obsessed with data structures and
algorithms because that's what some
Korean companies ask on their interview
which sometimes is good sometimes it's
bad but even if you don't want to go on
an interview there are solution
algorithms are good to learn because
again they make they keep you're sharp
in your brain no you can be a Android
developer without knowing Java that's
what we have coding so going checkout
cotton Java the Java domination is
coming to an end on Android thankfully
right so this is a question gyah what
the heck mean this is a question that I
get a lot in that the answer is not
learn C or learn Python if you want to
become a security specialist you need to
understand how systems work you need to
understand how connections work need to
understand how servers work how
computers work how ports work you need
to understand basically in
firm antics like the computer science
part I will recommend you to learn Linux
become very good at Linux and not Kali
Linux but again there's not one
programming language Jesus
you could hug with any programming
language the point is in turn the
standard systems around it this question
is very specific like variable names and
how to name them but actually what this
is about is about software quality so
for this I will recommend you a book
that is called code complete code
complete talks about this talk about
software quality how to structure
projects how to name classes how to get
requirements from the client oh I will
100% recommend that book if you are
looking to improve your software quality
yes you should learn English 100 percent
there is no no question about it I
English is not my native language but
thanks to English I am able to do
everything that I'm able to do and I'm
able to learn everything that I know
because of English so 100 percent go out
and learn English I don't know how you
tell if somebody's feet for programming
it's not about your feet and you are not
it's about more like how do you feel
when your program do you feel like it's
your element do you feel passionate
about it do you like what you do do you
like the result do you like seeing
something on the screen are you good at
sitting down in a computer for 10 hours
every day those sorts of things are
better questions to us rather than say
are you good at programming or are you
fit for programming I think if you don't
want to be replaced yes you need to
start a little learn programming a
publishing is not enough anymore
unfortunately you need to at least be
able to know what JavaScript is also
it's a good it's a good thing to have if
you're a publisher and you know very
well CSS and you know how to make
beautiful designs
if you complement that with JavaScript
it's gonna be amazing you can build
beautiful interactive stuff the
programming language that you start with
does not matter the point is that you
should start so that's what people don't
realize you don't need to choose the
right programming language it is not a
marriage you are not gonna get married
to that programming language you can
learn Python first and then move to C or
you can start with rust and then move to
go do you don't need to overthink where
to start the point is you need to start
have
said this the easier programming
language to start with is even Python or
something more web focused like HTML CSS
JavaScript so yeah there's some
programming languages that are easier
for beginners I would never make a
beginner start with C or I would never
make a beginner start with Java that's
too much that's crazy
people ask the question about V J's
versus react listen I'm a react guy my
courses aren't react and I love react
and that's the only thing I learned I
did learn of UGS and a look into V J's
but for me react put money on the table
many many companies are using react
react is powered by Facebook so the
community is amazing most of the startup
that I follow use react so I don't know
but if I had to choose I will choose to
start with react 100% ok many people are
not going to like this answer but I
prefer mark rather than Windows because
of the hardware because of the mouse and
because of the console because it's a
UNIX based system now I don't like Apple
as a company because they are doing
things that I don't agree with but
hardware wise and software wise and
console wise I really think Mac OS is
superior to Windows you can do
programming with MacBook Air MacBook Air
is a good computer I mean you can do
programming with slow computers
programming is just writing text on a
screen so there's nothing more
lightweight than that now the question
would be what kind of programming do you
want to do do you want to program video
games do you want to program iOS and
Android applications because if you need
one to do those things you're going to
have to run simulators and that's where
your computer will start to sweat if you
want to make websites if you want to
make backends in front and a MacBook Air
is more than perfect to program 13-inch
15 inch 17 inch go with the biggest
screen you can afford your eyes will
appreciate it I'll have a 15-inch
MacBook Pro but also I have a separate
display that I use I don't program on
the MacBook Pro only because now it's
too small for my eyes and I love big
screens so yeah maybe just a small
laptop but buy a big display so you can
program and your eyes will appreciate I
think to become a good developer you
need to be humble
always you always need to be learning
you should never be
that you know you should always be
studying you should always listen to
feedback and it doesn't matter if you
have 10 years of experience you still
can learn from somebody that has six
months of experience and I think that's
something that some developers forget
they forget that we should all stay with
a mindset of beginners we should always
ask questions we should always listen
listen it doesn't matter if you have
five years of experience ten years of
experience whatever it is we should
always be students always feel like a
newbie and always feel like you don't
know anything and be aware of the amount
of things you don't know that's very
important because that makes you a
humble person all right thank you so
much for all the comments thank you for
the questions I know there are many that
I didn't answer in the video but don't
worry I'm gonna go in the comments and
answer them with my keyboard and now I
have a question for you my question
would be what sort of videos you would
like to see on the channel I can talk
about almost anything related to
computer programming languages advice
for programmers freelancing traveling as
a programmer hacking anything what do
you wanna learn let me know in the
comments thank you so much for your love
I appreciate it
stay safe don't forget to be happy don't
forget to the kimchi comes Anita Simon
hey-oh and bye bye